http://www.beckstonesartgallery.co.uk/index.php/item/2553-privacy-notice.html

Beckstones Art Gallery Ltd Privacy Notice 20/5/18
Beckstones Art Gallery Ltd is committed to protecting the privacy and security of your personal information.
This privacy notice describes how we collect and use personal information about you during and after your relationship with us, in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).
It applies to all service users, except children and those who do not have capacity.
Beckstones Art Gallery is a "data controller". This means that we are responsible for deciding how we hold and use personal information about you. We are required under data protection legislation to notify you of the information contained in this privacy notice.
This notice does not form part of any contract with you. We may update this notice at any time but if we do so, we will provide you with an updated copy of this notice as soon as reasonably practical.
It is important that you read this notice, together with any other privacy notice we may provide on specific occasions when we are collecting or processing personal information about you, so that you are aware of how and why we are using such information and what your rights are under the data protection legislation.
Data protection principles
We will comply with data protection law. This says that the personal information we hold about you must be:
Used lawfully, fairly and in a transparent way.
Collected only for valid purposes that we have clearly explained to you and not used in any way that is incompatible with those purposes.
Relevant to the purposes we have told you about and limited only to those purposes.
Accurate and kept up to date.
Kept only as long as necessary for the purposes we have told you about.
Kept securely.
The kind of information we hold about you
We may collect, store and use of personal information about you including the following categories:
Personal contact details such as name, title, addresses, telephone numbers, and personal email addresses
Transaction details.
Specific artists of interest to you
How is your personal information collected?
We collect personal information about you directly from you.
We may collect additional personal information in the course of our relationship with you.
How we will use information about you
We will only use your personal information when the law allows us to. Most commonly, we will use your personal information in the following circumstances:
Where we need to perform the contract we have entered into with you.
Where we need to comply with a legal obligation.
Situations in which we will use your personal information
We need all the categories of information in the list above primarily to allow us to perform our contract with you (or made on your behalf) and to enable us to comply with legal obligations. In some cases we may use your personal information to pursue legitimate interests, provided your interests and fundamental rights do not override those interests. The situations in which we will process your personal information include the following:
Making a decision about a request for you to use our services/be supplied with our goods.
To take/process/administer payment.
To provide the services/goods that we offer to you.
Administering the contract we have entered into with you or on your behalf.
With your consent, for marketing our services to you and keeping you informed on the services we offer, events and developments within the organisation.
Change of purpose
We will only use your personal information for the purposes for which we collected it, unless we reasonably consider that we need to use it for another reason and that reason is compatible with the original purpose. If we need to use your personal information for an unrelated purpose, we will notify you and we will explain the legal basis which allows us to do so.
Please note that we may process your personal information without your knowledge or consent, in compliance with the above rules, where this is required or permitted by law.
Data security
We have put in place appropriate security measures to prevent your personal information from being accidentally lost, used or accessed in an unauthorised way, altered or disclosed. Details of these measures are available upon request. We have put in place procedures to deal with any suspected data security breach and will notify you and any applicable regulator of a suspected breach where we are legally required to do so.
We will only retain your personal information for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for. Details of retention periods for different aspects of your personal information are available in our Retention Policy which is available upon request
Rights of access, correction, erasure, and restriction
Your duty to inform us of changes
It is important that the personal information we hold about you is accurate and current. Please keep us informed if your personal information changes during your relationship with us.
Your rights in connection with personal information
Under certain circumstances, by law you have the right to:
Request access to your personal information. This enables you to receive a copy of the personal information we hold about you and to check that we are lawfully processing it.
Request correction of the personal information that we hold about you. This enables you to have any incomplete or inaccurate information we hold about you corrected.
Request erasure of your personal information. This enables you to ask us to delete or remove personal information where there is no good reason for us continuing to process it. You also have the right to ask us to delete or remove your personal information where you have exercised your right to object to processing (see below).
Object to processing of your personal information where we are relying on a legitimate interest (or those of a third party) and there is something about your particular situation which makes you want to object to processing on this ground. You also have the right to object where we are processing your personal information for direct marketing purposes.
Request the restriction of processing of your personal information. This enables you to ask us to suspend the processing of personal information about you, for example if you want us to establish its accuracy or the reason for processing it.
Request the transfer of your personal information to another party.
If you want to review, verify, correct or request erasure of your personal information, object to the processing of your personal data, or request that we transfer a copy of your personal information to another party, please contact us in writing or by emailing This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
Right to withdraw consent
In the limited circumstances where you may have provided your consent to the collection, processing and transfer of your personal information for a specific purpose, you have the right to withdraw your consent for that specific processing at any time. To withdraw your consent, please contact us in writing or by emailing This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it. Once we have received notification that you have withdrawn your consent, we will no longer process your information for the purpose or purposes you originally agreed to, unless we have another legitimate basis for doing so in law.
Changes to this privacy notice
We reserve the right to update this privacy notice at any time, and we will provide you with a new privacy notice when we make any substantial updates. We may also notify you in other ways from time to time about the processing of your personal information.
back to top
Search by Tags - click on one below
Ambleside
Ashness Bridge
Ballet
Birds
Blea Tarn
Blencathra
Opening Hours
We are delighted to be opening again from December.
Winter Opening HoursFriday, Saturday & Sunday10.30 - 16:30
We are also very happy to open by appointment to fit in with your visit - please ring 01768 483601 or email.
Please wear face coverings and hand sanitiser will be available before entering the gallery. Please maintain social distancing in the gallery, admittance may be restricted at times depending on visitor numbers.
Gift Vouchers
Looking for a gift and spoilt for choice - how about one of our Gift Vouchers? Contact the Gallery for details.Artists
Dennis Rothwell BaileyDarren BakerRichard BarrettRendor BergerGeorge BusbyAlistair Butt
RSMAGeoff Butterworth
FRSA
BWSEileen ClarkPeter ClarkStephen Darbishire
RBAJohannes EerdmansDavid FarrenTim GustardClare HaleyTobias HarrisonThomas HeesakkersEdward HerseyChris Holland
GRADavid Howell
PPRSMAJoe HushAntonio IannicelliMargie JohnsonRobert LittlefordTrevor LingardStuart LongJulian MasonClive McCartneyGed MitchellJames NaughtonGerhard NesvadbaRex PrestonBob Richardson
PSKeith Richens
RSMAJim RidoutRob RitchieSheryl RobertsGeoff RollinsonMario SanzoneGudrun SibbonsHoward ShinglerHeinz SchölnhammerPeter SymondsAndrew TalbotAlan ThompsonMarc ThouyJohn TrickettPatricia TurnerGraham TwyfordBen WaddamsRobert WalkerCarl WhitfieldGlynn WilliamsRod Willis
Newsletter
Please enter your details if you would like to receive updates from Beckstones.
Beckstones Art Gallery, Greystoke Ghyll, Nr. Penrith, Cumbria CA11 0UQTelephone: 01768 483601
Opening Times: Monday 10am - 5pm; Wednesday 10am - 5pm; Friday 10am - 5pm; Saturday 10am - 5pm; Sunday 10am - 5pm
